STEPHANIE [GIGGLING]:
Oh, Leonard.
[LEONARD LAUGHING]
[PHONE RINGS]
STEPHANIE: You've reached
Dr. Stephanie Barnett. Leave a message.
[PHONE BEEPS]
HOWARD:
Hey, it's me again. Howard.
(Howard(voice):)Listen, my cousins from Fort Lauderdale
are flying in to meet you...
(Howard(voice):)...so that means we're gonna have to
move the dinner to a restaurant.
MRS. WOLOWITZ [SHOUTING OVER PHONE]:
Tell her we're going to the Olive Garden.
(Howard's Mother(voice):)I have a coupon from the paper.
HOWARD:
We're not going to the Olive Garden, Ma.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Oh, Mr. Big-Shot with his Red Lobster.
HOWARD: I'll call you back
when we firm up the details.
(Howard(voice):)It's Howard.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
- New shirts?
- Yeah, a couple.
PENNY: Nice.
- Thank you.
(Penny:)So who's the girl?